<dashboard>
  <label>About</label>
  <row>
    <html>
      <h2>$$APP_NAME</h2>
      <p>Version $$APP_VERSION</p>
      <p>Copyright © 2017 Cisco and/or its affiliates. All rights reserved.</p>
    </html>
  </row>
  <row>
    <html>
      <div style="width: 800px; margin: 0 auto 0 auto;">
        <h2 style="text-align: center;">End User License Agreement</h2>
        <p><b>IMPORTANT: PLEASE READ THIS END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT CAREFULLY. IT IS VERY IMPORTANT THAT YOU CHECK THAT YOU ARE OBTAINING CISCO SOFTWARE FROM AN APPROVED SOURCE AND THAT YOU, OR THE ENTITY YOU REPRESENT (COLLECTIVELY, THE “CUSTOMER”) HAVE COMPLETED ALL REQUIRED REGISTRATION AS THE END USER FOR THE PURPOSES OF THIS END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT.</b></p>
        <p>CISCO SYSTEMS, INC. OR ITS SUBSIDIARY LICENSING THE SOFTWARE INSTEAD OF CISCO SYSTEMS, INC. (“CISCO”) IS WILLING TO LICENSE THIS SOFTWARE TO YOU ONLY UPON THE CONDITION THAT YOU OBTAINED THE SOFTWARE FROM AN APPROVED SOURCE AND THAT YOU ACCEPT ALL OF THE TERMS CONTAINED IN THIS END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT (THE “AGREEMENT”). BY DOWNLOADING, INSTALLING, OR USING THE SOFTWARE, YOU ARE REPRESENTING THAT YOU ARE BINDING YOURSELF AND THE ENTITY YOU REPRESENT TO THE AGREEMENT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ALL OF THE TERMS OF THE AGREEMENT, THEN CISCO IS UNWILLING TO LICENSE THE SOFTWARE TO YOU AND YOU MAY NOT DOWNLOAD, INSTALL OR USE THE SOFTWARE. FOR THE PURPOSES OF THIS END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT, AN “APPROVED SOURCE” MEANS (A) CISCO; OR (B) A DISTRIBUTOR/RESELLER OR TECHNOLOGY PARTNER AUTHORIZED BY CISCO TO DISTRIBUTE THE SOFTWARE.</p>
        <p><b><i>License.</i></b> Conditioned upon compliance with the terms and conditions of the Agreement, Cisco grants to Customer a nonexclusive license to use the Software and Documentation for use with the third party software product, Splunk Enterprise, and solely for Customer’s internal business purposes. “Documentation” means written information (whether contained in user or technical manuals, training materials, specifications or otherwise) pertaining to the Software and made available by an Approved Source with the Software in any manner (including on CD-Rom, or on-line). In order to use the Software, Customer may be required to input a registration number or product authorization key and register Customer’s copy of the Software online at Cisco’s website to obtain the necessary license key or license file.</p>
        <p><b><i>General Limitations.</i></b> This is a license, not a transfer of ownership or title, to the Software and Documentation, and Cisco retains ownership of the intellectual property in and to the Software and Documentation. Customer acknowledges that the Software and Documentation contain trade secrets of Cisco or its suppliers or licensors, including but not limited to, the specific internal design and structure of individual programs and associated interface information. Cisco has no obligation to provide Customer with technical support for the Software under this Agreement or otherwise. Customer may modify the Software solely in connection with the use of the Splunk Enterprise software product. Except as otherwise expressly provided under the Agreement, Customer specifically agrees not to:</p>
        <p>(i) transfer, assign or sublicense its license rights to any other person, and Customer acknowledges that any attempted transfer, assignment, sublicense or use shall be void;</p>
        <p>(ii) publish any results of benchmark tests run on the Software;</p>
        <p>(iii) use or permit the Software to be used to perform services for third parties, whether on a service bureau or time sharing basis or otherwise, without the express written authorization of Cisco; or</p>
        <p>(iv) disclose, provide, or otherwise make available trade secrets contained within the Software and Documentation in any form to any third party without the prior written consent of Cisco. Customer shall implement reasonable security measures to protect such trade secrets.</p>
        <p><b><i>Proprietary Notices.</i></b> Customer agrees to maintain and reproduce all copyright, proprietary, and other notices on all copies, in any form, of the Software and Documentation in the same form and manner that such copyright and other proprietary notices are included on the Software and Documentation. Except as expressly authorized in the Agreement, Customer shall not make any copies or duplicates of any Software without the prior written permission of Cisco.</p>
        <p><b><i>Term and Termination.</i></b> The Agreement and the license granted herein shall remain effective until terminated. Customer may terminate the Agreement and the license at any time by destroying all copies of Software and any Documentation. Customer’s rights under the Agreement will terminate immediately without notice from Cisco if Customer fails to comply with any provision of the Agreement. Upon termination, Customer shall destroy all copies of Software and Documentation in its possession or control. All confidentiality obligations of Customer, all restrictions and limitations imposed on the Customer under the section titled “General Limitations” and all limitations of liability and disclaimers and restrictions of warranty shall survive termination of this Agreement. In addition, the provisions of the sections titled “U.S. Government End User Purchasers” shall survive termination of the Agreement.</p>
        <p><b><i>Export, Re-Export, Transfer and Use Controls.</i></b> The Software, Documentation and technology or direct products thereof (hereafter referred to as Software and Technology), supplied by Cisco under the Agreement are subject to export controls under the laws and regulations of the United States (U.S.) and any other applicable countries’ laws and regulations. Customer shall comply with such laws and regulations governing export, re- export, transfer and use of Cisco Software and Technology and will obtain all required U.S. and local authorizations, permits, or licenses. Cisco and Customer each agree to provide the other information, support documents, and assistance as may reasonably be required by the other in connection with securing authorizations or licenses. Information regarding compliance with export, re-export, transfer and use may be located at the following URL:</p>
        <p><a href="http://www.cisco.com/web/about/doing_business/legal/global_export_trade/general_export/contract_compliance.html">http://www.cisco.com/web/about/doing_business/legal/global_export_trade/general_export/contract_compliance.html</a>.</p>
        <p><b><i>U.S. Government End User Purchasers.</i></b> The Software and Documentation qualify as “commercial items,” as that term is defined at Federal Acquisition Regulation (“FAR”) (48 C.F.R.) 2.101, consisting of “commercial computer software” and “commercial computer software documentation” as such terms are used in FAR 12.212. Consistent with FAR 12.212 and DoD FAR Supp. 227.7202-1 through 227.7202-4, and notwithstanding any other FAR or other contractual clause to the contrary in any agreement into which the Agreement may be incorporated, Customer may provide to Government end user or, if the Agreement is direct, Government end user will acquire, the Software and Documentation with only those rights set forth in the Agreement. Use of either the Software or Documentation or both constitutes agreement by the Government that the Software and Documentation are “commercial computer software” and “commercial computer software documentation,” and constitutes acceptance of the rights and restrictions herein.</p>
        <p><b><i>Disclaimer of Warranty.</i> THE SOFWARE AND DOCUMENTATION ARE PROVIDED “AS-IS” WITH NO WARRANTIES. ALL EXPRESS OR IMPLIED CONDITIONS, REPRESENTATIONS, AND WARRANTIES INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTY OR CONDITION OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, NON- INFRINGEMENT, SATISFACTORY QUALITY, NON-INTERFERENCE, ACCURACY OF INFORMATIONAL CONTENT, OR ARISING FROM A COURSE OF DEALING, LAW, USAGE, OR TRADE PRACTICE, ARE HEREBY EXCLUDED TO THE EXTENT ALLOWED BY APPLICABLE LAW AND ARE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMED BY CISCO, ITS SUPPLIERS AND LICENSORS. IN ADDITION, CISCO MAKES NO WARRANTY WITH RESPECT TO THE SPLUNK ENTERPRISE SOFTWARE PRODUCT AND HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES RELATED THERETO.</b></p>
        <p><b><i>Limitation of Liability.</i></b> NOTWITHSTANDING ANYTHING ELSE IN THE AGREEMENT TO THE CONTRARY, ALL LIABILITY OF CISCO, ITS AFFILIATES, OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, SUPPLIERS AND LICENSORS COLLECTIVELY, TO CUSTOMER, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), BREACH OF WARRANTY OR OTHERWISE, SHALL NOT EXCEED THE PRICE PAID BY CUSTOMER TO ANY APPROVED SOURCE FOR THE SOFTWARE LICENSED HEREUNDER. THIS LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR SOFTWARE IS CUMULATIVE AND NOT PER INCIDENT (I.E. THE EXISTENCE OF TWO OR MORE CLAIMS WILL NOT ENLARGE THIS LIMIT).</p>
        <p><b><i>Waiver of Consequential Damages.</i></b> IN NO EVENT WILL CISCO OR ITS SUPPLIERS OR LICENSORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOST REVENUE, PROFIT, OR LOST OR DAMAGED DATA, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF CAPITAL, OR FOR SPECIAL, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES HOWEVER CAUSED AND REGARDLESS OF THE THEORY OF LIABILITY OR WHETHER ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE SOFTWARE OR OTHERWISE AND EVEN IF CISCO OR ITS SUPPLIERS OR LICENSORS HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.</p>
        <p>Customer acknowledges and agrees that Cisco is providing the Software and Documentation on an “AS-IS” basis and thus has entered into the Agreement in reliance upon the disclaimers of warranty and the limitations of liability set forth herein, that the same reflect an allocation of risk between the parties (including the risk that a contract remedy may fail of its essential purpose and cause consequential loss), and that the same form an essential basis of the bargain between the parties.</p>
        <p><b><i>Controlling Law, Jurisdiction.</i></b> This Agreement is controlled by and construed under the laws of the State of California, United States of America, notwithstanding any conflicts of law provisions; and the state and federal courts of California shall have exclusive jurisdiction over any claim arising under the Agreement. If you obtained the Software in Canada, unless expressly prohibited by local law, the Agreement is controlled by and construed under the laws of the Province of Ontario, Canada, notwithstanding any conflicts of law provisions; and the courts of the Province of Ontario shall have exclusive jurisdiction over any claim arising under the Agreement. If you obtained the Software in Europe, the Middle East, Africa, Asia or Oceania (excluding Australia), unless expressly prohibited by local law, the Agreement is controlled by and construed under the laws of England, notwithstanding any conflicts of law provisions; and the English courts shall have exclusive jurisdiction over any claim arising under the Agreement. In addition, if the Agreement is controlled by the laws of England, no person who is not a party to the Agreement shall be entitled to enforce or take the benefit of any of its terms under the Contracts (Rights of Third Parties) Act 1999. If you obtained the Software in Japan, unless expressly prohibited by local law, the Agreement is controlled by and construed under the laws of Japan, notwithstanding any conflicts of law provisions; and the Tokyo District Court of Japan shall have exclusive jurisdiction over any claim arising under the Agreement. If you obtained the Software in Australia, unless expressly prohibited by local law, the Agreement is controlled by and construed under the laws of the State of New South Wales, Australia, notwithstanding any conflicts of law provisions; and the State and federal courts of New South Wales shall have exclusive jurisdiction over any claim arising under the Agreement. If you obtained the Software in any other country, unless expressly prohibited by local law, the Agreement is controlled by and construed under the laws of the State of California, United States of America, notwithstanding any conflicts of law provisions; and the state and federal courts of California shall have exclusive jurisdiction over any claim arising under the Agreement.</p>
        <p>The parties specifically disclaim the application of the UN Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods. Notwithstanding the foregoing, either party may seek interim injunctive relief in any court of appropriate jurisdiction with respect to any alleged breach of such party’s intellectual property or proprietary rights. If any portion hereof is found to be void or unenforceable, the remaining provisions of the Agreement shall remain in full force and effect. Except as expressly provided herein, the Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between the parties with respect to the license of the Software and Documentation and supersedes any conflicting or additional terms contained in any purchase order or elsewhere, all of which terms are excluded. The Agreement has been written in the English language, and the parties agree that the English version will govern.</p>
      </div>
    </html>
  </row>
  <row>
    <html>
      <h2>Change Log</h2>
      <ul>
      </ul>
    </html>
  </row>
</dashboard>
