<dashboard>
  <label>Documentation</label>
  
  <row>
    <html>
      <h2>$$APP_NAME Help</h2>
      <ul>
        <li><a href="#upgrading">Upgrading the App</a></li>
        <li><a href="#dash">Dashboards</a></li>
        <ul>
          <li><a href="#dash1">eStreamer Summary</a></li>
          <li><a href="#dash2">Sensor Summary</a></li>
          <li><a href="#dash3">Policy Summary</a></li>
          <li><a href="#dash4">Host Summary</a></li>
          <li><a href="#dash8">Flow Summary</a></li>
          <li><a href="#dash5">Intrusion Event Summary</a></li>
          <li><a href="#dash6">File / Malware Event Summary</a></li>
          <li><a href="#dash7">Correlation Event Summary</a></li>
        </ul>
        <li><a href="#search">Searching</a></li>
        <li><a href="#actions">Event Actions</a></li>
        <ul>
          <li><a href="#action1">eStreamer: Save PCAP</a></li>
          <li><a href="#action2">eStreamer: View Event</a></li>
          <li><a href="#action3">eStreamer: View Connection</a></li>
        </ul>
      </ul>
    </html>
  </row>
  
  <row>
    <html>
      <a name="upgrading" /><h2>Upgrading the App</h2>
      <p>Before installing an upgrade to the app, it is recommended to disable the eStreamer
        client prior to the upgrade and to wait for it to stop before continuing.  This can
        be done from the app Setup page.  Ensure sure the "Upgrade app" check box is
        selected when installing the app package.  Once the upgrade has been completed, and
        Splunk restarted, the client can be re-enabled from the Setup page.</p>
    </html>
  </row>
  
  <row>
    <html>
      <a name="dash" /><h2>Dashboards</h2>
      <p>There are five dashboards provided by the app. Each of them gives a different
        high-level view of the data being provided by eStreamer from the Defense Center.
        It's important to note that each of the dashboards has a time selector at the top
        of the screen that allows for a change of the time period represented in the
        dashboard. Below is a brief description of each of the dashboards:</p>
      
      <a name="dash1" /><h4>eStreamer Summary</h4>
      <p>This dashboard provides an overview of the state of the eStreamer client, counts
        of the important eStreamer records being seen, and a timeline view of the records
        coming into Splunk.</p>

      <a name="dash2" /><h4>Sensor Summary</h4>
      <p>This dashboard shows the distribution of events across the managed devices and
        security zones that are defined on each device. At the bottom of the dashboard is
        a sorted list of each device, and its associated interfaces and security zones.
        The devices with the most hits are displayed first.</p>

      <a name="dash3" /><h4>Policy Summary</h4>
      <p>This dashboard shows the distribution of events across the access control
        policies, access control policy rules, and intrusion policies. This middle of
        the dashboard is a sorted list of each device, and its associated policies and
        rules. The devices with the most hits are displayed first. The bottom of the
        dashboard provides the distribution of events across the correlation policies
        and rules.</p>

      <a name="dash4" /><h4>Host Summary</h4>
      <p>This dashboard shows the geographic region of the source and destination
        addresses involved in events, where possible. It's important to note that IP
        addresses in the RFC1918 space, or other reserved block, will not properly map.
        Next come sorted lists of the most frequently involved source and destination
        addresses, then a sorted list showing the most frequently involved source and
        destination address pairs. Lastly comes the most frequently involved ports, both
        as a source and a destination.</p>

      <a name="dash8" /><h4>Flow Summary</h4>
      <p>This dashboard shows detail about network connections being seen by the sensors.
        It provides a breakdown by application protocols, client applications, web
        applications, and detail about sensor, policy, and rule hit distributions.</p>

      <a name="dash5" /><h4>Intrusion Event Summary</h4>
      <p>This dashboard shows the timeline of events coming into Splunk, as well as the
        distribution of events across the devices, priorities, impacts, and IPS block
        results. At the bottom of the dashboard is a sorted list of the most frequently
        hit signatures and signature classifications.</p>

      <a name="dash6" /><h4>File / Malware Event Summary</h4>
      <p>This dashboard shows the timeline of events coming into Splunk, as well as the
        distribution of events across the devices, actions, disposition, and file types.
        At the bottom of the dashboard is a sorted list of the most frequently seen
        files.</p>

      <a name="dash7" /><h4>Correlation Event Summary</h4>
      <p>This dashboard shows the timeline of events coming into Splunk, as well as the
        distribution of events across the devices, policies, event types, and blocks.
        At the bottom of the dashboard is a sorted list of the most frequently seen
        correlations.</p>
    </html>
  </row>
  
  <row>
    <html>
      <a name="search" /><h2>Searching</h2>
      <p>eStreamer for Splunk puts logs into a dedicated index named estreamer. This
        means that searches against the eStreamer data must use <tt>index=estreamer</tt>.
        There are also two distinct source types associated with this app:
        <tt>eStreamer</tt> and <tt>client_check</tt>. All eStreamer logs use the
        <tt>eStreamer</tt> source type, where only eStreamer client status messages use
        the <tt>client_check</tt> source type.</p>
      <p>The <b>Search</b> menu provides quick access the different event searches, as well as
        IP address, port, and user profiling searches.</p>
    </html>
  </row>

  <row>
    <html>
      <a name="actions" /><h2>Event Actions</h2>
      <p>eStreamer for Splunk adds three items to the <b>Event Actions</b> menu available
        in searches:</p>
        
      <a name="action1" /><h4>eStreamer: Save PCAP</h4>
      <p>This action will only work for PACKET eStreamer records
        (<tt>rec_type_simple=PACKET</tt>). It takes the values of the <tt>event_id</tt>
        and <tt>packet</tt> fields and decodes the hex encoded packet, returning a PCAP
        as a downloadable file using the event ID for the filename (for example,
        5110.pcap). It is important to note that the <b>Log packets</b> setting must be
        enabled for this Event Action to be of use.</p>
        
      <a name="action2" /><h4>eStreamer: View Event</h4>
      <p>This action will work for any log containing the <tt>event_id</tt> field.  It
        will open a new search looking for any logs with the same event ID value.</p>
        
      <a name="action3" /><h4>eStreamer: View Connection</h4>
      <p>This action will work for any log containing the <tt>instance_id</tt> and
        <tt>connection_id</tt> fields.  It will open a new search looking for any
        logs with the same connection values.</p>
    </html>
  </row>
  
</dashboard>